Another Tuesday morning,
same old routine.
The vanity mirror,
a shallow scene.
They're tradin' secrets,
whispers in the hall.
Did you see what she was wearin'?
It's just awful,
y'all.
Pink manicures and little white lies,
they spend their whole damn paycheck on what money buys.
Little bows and kitten heels,
scared to break a sweat.
Oh,
they call it livin',
but they haven't learned to live yet.
'Cause real women drive Jeeps,
baby,
rooftop down,
tearin' up the blacktop all over this town.
Got the sun in our faces,
dust in our hair.
Don't need a paved road 'cause we don't really care.
Spinnin' the tires on a path of our own,
got the radio blastin',
drivin' hard to the bone.
Yeah,
real women drive Jeeps,
can you hear that sound?
The only gossip we're spreadin' is the bass that shakes the ground.
They're filterin' pictures till their skin is pristine.
Afraid of a smudge,
afraid of what's real and mean.
Obsessed with the weight on that digital scale,
their biggest problem is a broken fingernail.
They spend all their hours just tryna fit the mold,
another copy of a story that's already told.
Hidin' from the weather,
shieldin' their complexion,
just a fragile little doll cravin' cheap affection.
'Cause real women drive Jeeps,
baby,
rooftop down,
tearin' up the blacktop all over this town.
Got the sun in our faces,
dust in our hair.
Don't need a paved road 'cause we don't really care.
Spinnin' the tires on a path of our own,
got the radio blastin',
drivin' hard to the bone.
Yeah,
real women drive Jeeps,
can you hear that sound?
The only gossip we're spreadin' is the bass that shakes the ground.
Real women drive Jeeps.
Rooftop down.